DIMITRIS KONSTANTINOU

Limassol, Cyprus | (357) 96090943 demis.konstantinou16@gmail.com | <u>LinkedIn</u> | <u>Github</u>

PROFILE

Senior/Lead Blockchain developer with over 3 years of development and security experience in Solidity, Foundry, Hardhat and Slither. Past experience in deploying and optimizing smart contracts using various protocols (ERC1155, ERC721, ERC1400, ERC3643, ERC4337, ERC20) as well as openzeppelin libraries (Base64, Upgradeable, Math, SafeERC, Governance and more). Active open-source contributor(Slither, Optimism Bridge, Ender liquid staking), auditor and hackathon participant also proficient in Yul, Cairo, Move, threaded solidity and some rust (C++ was my first language)

EXPERIENCE

IntellectFU

Lead Blockchain Developer | July 2023 - Current

- Worked on large scale Defi projects leading teams from concept to delivery
- Mentored multiple junior solidity developers and other developers transitioning into blockchain
- Deployed multiple blockchain networks such as besu and private testnets, and leveraged cross chain messaging protocols such as LayerZero to transfer data between chains and contracts
- Developed and deployed multiple Securities related smart contracts for various tier 0 companies with a large TVL (50m+)
- Led the PolygonzZKEVM team and researched quantum proof alternatives to ECDSA signatures

Inverse

Lead Blockchain Developer | September 2022 – June 2023

- Developed and deployed the initial ERC 721 smart contracts
- Developed and deployed the staking contract for the NFT game
- Created a back-end service along with AWS for the WeBGL NFT game
- Oversaw the website creation and connected the smart contracts
- Audited and optimized the smart contracts used for the NFT game

Nethermind

Smart Contract Auditor Contractor | July 2022 - October 2022

- Audited MEVs, Vault contracts, AMMs and Cairo projects alongside the core auditing team
- Generated documentation, gas optimization change reports and used various security tools such as Echidna and slither for detecting vulnerabilities.

The Ramen Shop NFT, Printers NFT, Huevos NFT, Dopa Token

Smart Contract Developer | January 2021 – July 2022

- Develop NFT contracts used by thousands and partnered with over 30 Ramen shops internationally
 as one of the first NFT projects with real life utility.
- Developed NFT minting contracts, ERC20 contracts and staking contracts for various companies and individuals during the 2020 – 2022 NFT market
- Managed, maintained and optimized various smart contracts over a period of a year and a half performing monthly maintenance and consulting after contract deployment

Iarumas Holdings LTD, T & O Cyprus Planetarium, Creative Universe

Technical Director | January 2019 – July 2022

- I was responsible for the maintenance, upgrading and development of various software and networks for the 3 companies
- Leveraged Linux, C++, JavaScript and Python to perform security tasks
- Reviewed all hardware and software used by the CEO and sent by various companies for security purposes.
- Created a cross country secure communication service for the company to use with other high net worth clients

EDUCATION

Computing (Software Development) – Bath Spa University 2015- 2018

AWARDS AND ACKNOWLEDGEMENTS

- Contributed to Slither by trail of bits and various other large protocols and technologies (Optimism Bridge, Venom, Sui, Aptos) and was one of the first people to work with Cairo programming
- Received an award by IBM for our raspberry Pi Project that was showcased in Los Angeles
- Have worked on over 100+ smart contracts including liquid staking protocols, AMMs, MEVs, Swaps,
 NFts and more.